[
    {"question": "Bra", "answer": "Good","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dålig", "answer": "Bad","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stor", "answer": "Big","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Liten", "answer": "Small","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gammal", "answer": "Old","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ung", "answer": "Young","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vacker", "answer": "Beautiful","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ful", "answer": "Ugly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snabb", "answer": "Fast","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Långsam", "answer": "Slow","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hög", "answer": "High","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Låg", "answer": "Low","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tung", "answer": "Heavy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lätt", "answer": "Light","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kort", "answer": "Short","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lång", "answer": "Long","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tjock", "answer": "Thick","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tunn", "answer": "Thin","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ny", "answer": "New","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rik", "answer": "Rich","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Fattig", "answer": "Poor","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Glad", "answer": "Happy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ledsen", "answer": "Sad","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snygg", "answer": "Handsome","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Trevlig", "answer": "Nice","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Otrevlig", "answer": "Unpleasant","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rolig", "answer": "Funny","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tråkig", "answer": "Boring","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snäll", "answer": "Kind","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Elak", "answer": "Mean","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Modig", "answer": "Brave","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Feg", "answer": "Cowardly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stark", "answer": "Strong","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Svag", "answer": "Weak","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kall", "answer": "Cold","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varm", "answer": "Warm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Torr", "answer": "Dry","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Våt", "answer": "Wet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Mjuk", "answer": "Soft","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hård", "answer": "Hard","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Söt", "answer": "Sweet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bitter", "answer": "Bitter","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skarp", "answer": "Sharp","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dum", "answer": "Dumb","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Klok", "answer": "Clever","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lugn", "answer": "Calm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Orolig", "answer": "Worried","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tyst", "answer": "Quiet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Högljudd", "answer": "Loud","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Mörk", "answer": "Dark","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ljus", "answer": "Light","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tidig", "answer": "Early","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sen", "answer": "Late","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Nära", "answer": "Near","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Långt", "answer": "Afar","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Smal", "answer": "Narrow","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bred", "answer": "Broad","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hög", "answer": "Tall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Låg", "answer": "Short","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ren", "answer": "Clean","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Smutsig", "answer": "Dirty","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Frisk", "answer": "Healthy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sjuk", "answer": "Sick","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tjock", "answer": "Fat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Smal", "answer": "Slim","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vacker", "answer": "Pretty","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ful", "answer": "Ugly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snabb", "answer": "Quick","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Långsam", "answer": "Slow","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hög", "answer": "High","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Låg", "answer": "Low","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tung", "answer": "Heavy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lätt", "answer": "Light","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"}
]